http://winterlandinc.com/privacy-and-security/

Privacy and Security
Privacy and Security
We take privacy quite seriously
Winterland Incorporated recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: http://www.WinterlandInc.com. The site is owned and operated by Winterland.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at info@winterlandinc.com or by postal mail to:
Winterland, Inc.
1101 South Miller Avenue
Marion, Indiana 46953
765-664-3918
Identifying Information
In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. Generally, Winterland requests identifying information when you:
Register on any of our web sites
Place an order
Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion
Participate in a rebate program, contest, or other promotional offer
Request a special service
Request information or files from technical support or customer service
In these instances, Winterland will ask for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to “unsubscribe” to these mailings at any time.
What Winterland Will Do With Your Information
If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by Winterland and will only be used by Winterland to support your customer relationship with us. We will not add you to a mailing list, or newsletter without your registration for this service. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service.
What Others May Do With Your Information
Winterland does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time Winterland may use agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for Winterland (such as database maintenance or computer upgrades), however, they are required by us to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services for Winterland. In addition, Winterland may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our users.
Winterland On-line Store
The Winterland On-line Store is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your identifying information. If you choose, you can set up an account. This will allow you to have a customized order page for express ordering and to view your purchasing history. To protect your privacy, we have designed the Sites to include certain steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections in an account. You will always have access to this account information and can view it, update it or correct it at any time. To access your information, you will need to use a password.
When purchasing products through the our web site, the order form will also ask you to provide a daytime telephone number. However, the telephone number is only used to quickly resolve questions relative to an order, such as to clarify customer email addresses that are inactive, or entered incorrectly.
Third Party Links
Winterland Inc.com does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave Winterland Inc.com, Winterland cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site.
Cookies
At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a “cookie”. We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. We only use cookies to learn ways to enhance our Sites, and to give you better, more personalized service while in our web site. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is sent. However, some functions of the Sites will not function if you refuse cookies. These areas of our web site will have information posted about cookies, and when a cookie will be uploaded to your computer.
Changes to this Policy
Winterland may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can write to:
Winterland, Inc.
1101 South Miller Avenue
Marion, Indiana 46953
765-664-3918
Credit Card Security
We know customers are concerned about credit card security. We use one of the worlds largest funds transfer agencies and never store your credit card information locally. We gather just enough information to process the charge and then delete the details
Copyright © 2019, All rights reserved.
